kimberamerica.com 2010-05-24

# Kimber - 1911 Pistols & Rifles

Privacy Policy 

Kimber is committed to protecting your privacy. This Policy describes our practices regarding personal information collected through our web site. By using our web site, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described in this Policy or as the same may be amended or modified from time to time as indicated herein.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe and efficient web site experience. We collect information from our web site in several ways. The primary purpose for collecting and using personal information is to perform certain functions on your behalf, such as processing and ordering products or for filing a catalog request. We also collect certain financial information from users who order products from us. Except as indicated below, we will not disclose to others any of your personal information unless we have your express permission or in response to a court order or substantially similar legal procedure. We may disclose your information if we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

In some instances, we may collect non-personal information through cookies to help us improve the performance and effectiveness of our web site.

We will not sell or share your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes absent your permission to do so. We may share your personal information with authorized third parties agents or contractors to fulfill a service or transaction you requested such as when we need to ship our products to you. Since your personal security concerns are very important to us, we use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized use or disclosure.

While we will make every effort to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit and we recommend you take every precaution in protecting your personal information. We will keep your personal information only as long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and/or as required by applicable laws and regulations.

Our web site may provide links to other third party web sites which are outside of our control and not covered by our Policy. Links or advertisements to any third party or web site does not constitute or imply any endorsement of such website.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If we learn that we collected personal information of a child under the age of thirteen (13), we will delete that information from our systems.

We will occasionally update this Policy to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback.
